We just wrapped up two amazing days at
AI DevCon in London.
>> But the great [music] thing is that we
get to do it all over again in New York
City this November.
>> You're absolutely right. We're going to
be back in the city that never sleeps on
November 3rd and 4th for more amazing
sessions,
>> [music]
>> really engaging hands-on workshops, and
much more.
>> Yep, all that great networking,
partying, eating, and drinking that
you've come to expect from [music] AI
DevCon. We think we have one of the best
hallway tracks in the business, and
[music] it's the perfect complement to
our incredible speakers and presenters.
>> We'll both be in person and virtual with
live-streamed access to all main stage
keynotes and [music] talks.
>> Sign up right now for our super blind
bird ticket for just $100, only
available for a limited time.
>> We're really excited to be headed back
to the Big Apple. We hope to see you all
there.
>> [music]